mmm what is game B well not the most
difficult of all questions but a very
very very difficult question it's akin
to asking what is the Dow what is God
that kind of thing not that game B is
God that's that's not the point but it
is okay so if game a is a set of
individuals collaborating with each
other game B is a web of collaboration
made up of individuals doing so kind of
thing that the emphasis is completely
different so the basic premise of game B
is that it focuses on the space between
the individuals the relationships
between them and the web the
interconnectedness of the web
if game a is blasphemous and game B is
holy
it is the game that tries to reestablish
the holy symmetry between humanity and
nature realigning the Axis Mundi
but the anima Mundi may spin around it
to each their own axis how to realign
the spines of all the players of the
game be the source of good gameplay and
aligned spine and then a good spin a
holy idea I think is really important so
if if game a is gross and game B is holy
gain B honors the holes this is what
holy is right it's the holes it's the
spaces it's the lacunae right and so
again it's the space between that that
is that that is the crucial thing to
focus on and it's very very easy to
start thinking o crypto currencies would
be game B this kind of thing but no no
no no that's that's that that's missing
the point game B isn't concrete notions
of systems game B is the soil from which
emerges what needs to emerge that's
that's the point and so the creation of
game B is not about designing new
systems designing infrastructures it's
about allowing relations allowing
fertile relationships to create game B
is the game that removes power from the
Empire and gives it to culture the game
being is a game of social permaculture
permanent culture keeping the culture
inside of its self spinning trunk so we
can self-perpetuate rather than always
being blocked by the force of Empire
Dame B is the game that allows for
anyone to play the game that they need
to play to develop their highest player
self game B is a meta game there's not
one single game but is a plurality of
games which I derived from a set of
fundamental game principles and those
fundamental game principles are the
social permaculture right there and and
and so the
[Music]
fully conscious engagement in the
playing of games rather than having
invisible games playing you as pawns
rather the players engage with the game
fully consciously fully understanding
and and and accepting submitting to
don't quite like submitting to but
anyway the rules of the game but this
also places a great burden of
responsibility on the individual burden
is again not a great word because it
feels like it's a hard thing to bear
it's not like that but it does place a
great deal of responsibility on the
individual to make to be a good player
to be the kind of player that people
want to play games with and and so
personal development is a core feature
of game B game B is the game that aligns
personal and global development aim B is
the game which allows for the choice
between many different games which are
organized into guilds so that one may
find the games that best suit oneself on
an individual level but also oneself on
a communal level a game where wealth can
be part of a communal self which plays
in a way that one wants to play game B
is a process of cultivating game
awareness game B is a process of
cultivating ludo psycho technologies
game B is a process of cultivating
socio-psychological of alignment between
the personal game and the global game
and all of the stages in between the
fractal nature of game B is another key
feature of it
so the games
if you like is the infinite void and
games within games within games within
games within games are played within
that space and so be on a personal
individual level of development of one's
ability to play games includes an
understanding of the levels of games
above your immediate game of the above
the social game of the cultural game and
of the messer game itself which is the
formula imprinted in all of the games at
every Fraxel level game B is the meta
game that generates transparent games
games that one can you look into a one
can see what is being what is being
played with here what are the states
here how can I be accepted into this
game what are the doors that I need to
pass through are the doors at merit are
the doors privileged are the ghouls
family bloodline the generation of games
with clear pathways of initiation into
the higher levels game B facilitates the
distribution of resources along the
lines of different game rules some are
hierarchical some are cyclical some are
by chance but not one game to rule them
all game B isn't the game to rule them
all but it is vessel in which they all
sit kind of thing so game B is the
infinite game within which potentially
finite games can be embedded so the
finite game can still exist the wind
blues game can still exist but embedded
within the rare
the context of all of these games are
part of in the same way that within an
ecosystem you know in any given battle
between the line and the gazelle the
line or the gazelle wins but in the in
the grander scale the the the larger
game is the development of the
complexity and the capacity of the
ecosystem itself not of the line or of
the gazelle
you're muted Lawrence
game B is an ecosystem of games game B
is an ecosystem of consensual games
games that one and give oneself to one
can remove oneself from a game is not a
game if it is not consensual game a is a
game bullies of being forced to play
specific games games B is a game of
choosing which gains on once to play and
the quest again B is finding which games
are the ones which allow oneself realign
in which spine I say doing help realign
the Global's
you